Guide to the Edison Price Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Edison Price Papers
1937-1999
MS 2015
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
29.33
44 boxes
The collection is comprised of business and design records generated by the two lighting design, manufacturing, and consulting companies founded by Edison Price in New York, New York: Edison Price, Inc. (founded in 1952) and Nulux, Inc. (founded in 1990). Papers include both project and product records, as well as research files, patent documents, and general documentation about the firms. Project records consist of drawings, correspondence, and notes relating to lighting designs, including such projects as the Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library at Yale University, the Whitney Museum of Art, the Guggenheim Museum Bilbao, and the J. Paul Getty Center in Los Angeles. Product records consist of drawings, photometric reports, and other information for a range of fixtures designed and manufactured by Edison Price, Inc. and Nulux, Inc.
Price, Edison Avery, 1918-1997
Biographical / Historical
Named after the famed inventor, Thomas Alva Edison, Edison Avery Price (1918-1997) entered the field of lighting design through employment at Display Stage Lighting, Inc., a company founded by his father, William E. Price, in New York City in 1917. The younger Price worked at Display Stage Lighting, which specialized in theatrical lighting, from 1935 to 1946, and from 1946 to 1949 undertook the roles of Treasurer and Vice President in charge of design, development, and production at successor firm Display Lighting, Inc. Upon leaving the family business in 1949, Price operated as a self-employed lighting consultant. In 1952 he founded Edison Price, Inc., which grew from a small architectural lighting company based in a Manhattan loft to a design, manufacturing, and consulting firm whose roster of clients included Louis Kahn, Marcel Breuer, Ludwig Mies van der Rohe, Philip Johnson, I.M. Pei, Edward Larrabee Barnes, and Skidmore, Owings, & Merrill. Price provided services and fixtures for such renowned projects as Pei's Grand Louvre in Paris, Buckminster Fuller's geodesic dome at the Montreal 1967 Expo, Breuer's Whitney Museum, Mies and Johnson's Four Seasons Restaurant in the Seagram Building, and Kahn's Yale University Art Gallery, the last of which Price undertook in collaboration with his long-time associate, lighting consultant Richard Kelly. After leaving Edison Price, Inc., Price founded Nulux, Inc., in 1990.
Throughout his career, Price designed and manufactured his own products. He developed and customized lighting solutions and fixtures for specific architectural spaces, and employed individuals with similar design aesthetics to complete his company's designs, such as lighting engineer Isaac Goodbar. Simplicity was the hallmark of his fixtures, which tended to blend unobtrusively with the architectural setting. Continuous lighting tracks and recessed fixtures, for instance, were early innovations of the firm that became commonplaces of the industry. Price was expert at illuminating a variety of interiors, from offices and theaters, to museums and libraries.
In recognition of his contributions to the advancement of architectural lighting, Price was awarded the Richard Kelly Lifetime Achievement Award by the Illuminating Engineering Society and, in 1981, the AIA Medal by the American Institute of Architects.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Delia Price, 2014 and 2018.
Scope and Contents
The collection is comprised of business and design records generated by the two lighting design, manufacturing, and consulting companies founded by Edison Price in New York, New York: Edison Price, Inc. (founded in 1952) and Nulux, Inc. (founded in 1990). Papers include both project and product records, as well as research files, patent documents, and general documentation about the firms. Project records consist of drawings, correspondence, and notes relating to lighting designs, including such projects as the Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library at Yale University, the Whitney Museum of Art, the Guggenheim Museum Bilbao, and the J. Paul Getty Center in Los Angeles. Product records consist of drawings, photometric reports, and other information for a range of fixtures designed and manufactured by Edison Price, Inc. and Nulux, Inc.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in seven series: I. General Company Information, 1952-1999. II. Research Files and Notes, 1940-1999. III. Patents, 1950-1997. IV. Project Files, 1956-1998. V. Fixtures and Products, 1965-1999. VI. Slides, Negatives, and Photographs, 1953-1996. VII. Personal Papers, 1910-1986.
Separated Materials
Duplicate materials were removed from the collection.
Architecture, Modern -- 20th Century; Lighting, Architectural and decorative; Light in architecture; Interior lighting; Price, Delia; Price, Edison Avery, 1918-1997; Four Seasons (Restaurant); Seagram Building (New York, N.Y.); Yale University. Art Gallery; Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library; Whitney Museum of American Art; Upjohn Company; Illuminating Engineering Society; American Institute of Architects; Nulux, Inc.; Edison Price, Inc.
- General Company Information, 1952–1999; Series I
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains correspondence, financial records, and lists of projects generated by the two lighting design, manufacturing, and consulting companies founded by Edison Price in New York, New York: Edison Price, Inc. (founded in 1952) and Nulux, Inc. (founded in 1990). Also included are awards from the American Institute of Architects and Illuminating Engineering Society.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged by company. Folders within each company are arranged alphabetically.
  - Edison Price, Inc.
    - Articles, 1954, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Articles, 1952–2001 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Articles and clippings, 1966–1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Articles and writing, Illuminating Engineering Society Lighting Handbook, 1980, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Awards
      - American Institute of Architects Medal, 1976–1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - American Institute of Architects Medal, 1981 May (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Illuminating Engineering Society NA Medal, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Illuminating Engineering Society Richard Kelly Award, press releases and mailing lists, 1991–1992 (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
    - Catalog, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Certificate of incorporation, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Company history, 1968, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1970s-1980s (Box 1, Folder 12-13)
    - Correspondence, 1980s (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
    - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, thank you for projects, 1957–1997 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Financial, 1963, 1999, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - First quarter report, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Fixture sales information, 1978–1993 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Fixture price lists, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - List of projects, 1961–1985 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - List of projects, 1953-1988, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Project list, Innovative and Memorable Projects, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Organizational charts, 1979, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Public relations proposal, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Nulux, Inc.
    - Correspondence, 1990s (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Financial, 1994-1999, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - List of projects, 1993–1997 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Manufacturing equipment, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Names for fixtures, number system, and graphics, 1988-1990, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Visitor lists, 1992-1993, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Illuminating Engineering Society, "Pioneer of Light: Edison Avery Price", 1999 May 4 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Tribute to Edison Price by Brooks Bragdon, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Research Files and Notes, 1940–1999; Series II
  This series is primarily comprised of research files on lighting companies, designers, and equipment. Also included are daily and weekly lists of projects with status updates for Edison Price, Inc.'s early projects.
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  - Air Flow, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - American Home Lighting Institute
    - General, 1982–1984 (Box 4, Folder 2-3)
    - California, 1983–1984 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Chicago, 1984–1985 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Bowden Industries, Inc., Circa 1990s (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Bridgemarket, 1987–1988 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Chicago Plenum, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Code change, City of New York, 1978–1981 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Columbia Lighting, 1972–1974 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Fading, 1960–1982 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Flourescent fixtures, thermal performance, Undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - General Electric/Sylvania, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Goodbar, Isaac, Undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Hepworth Machine Co. Inc., tools for metal spinning, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Howard Brandston lighting design, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Jig to machine, pin cam nut, 1981–1984 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Kelly, Richard, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Kliegl Brothers, 1940-1954, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Leslie Company, catalog, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Lighting
    - Furniture, 1977-1979, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Museum, 1937, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Low Milliamp Operation, 1971–1975 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Manhattan Brass and Copper Co., Undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - National electrical code, 1983–1987 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - National electrical code proposal, 1984–1986 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Owens Corning Fiberglass Program, 1975, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Research, miscellaneous, 1964, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Study carrels, lighting, 1971–1972 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Super-Ellipse, Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Technical papers, lighting history, 1963–1993 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Weekly lists of projects and status updates for Edison Price, Inc., 1965–1973 (Box 7, Folder 1-7)
- Patents, 1950–1997; Series III
  This series contains correspondence to lawyers and lighting design companies, including Sylvan R. Shemitz and Associates, Inc., as well as research documentation pertaining to Edison Price's patent applications.
  This series is arranged by two groupings: general patent documentation and fixtures and products. Folders within each grouping are arranged alphabetically.
  - General
    - Correspondence, documentation, and research, Circa 1970s-1990s (Box 8, Folder 1-3)
    - Correspondence, documentation, and research, Circa 1980s-1990s (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Drawings, Undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Dropped applications, 1975, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Fixtures and products
    - Air bearing, 1984–1988 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Ceiling mount, 1967–1971 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Connector, 1980–1982 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Display mounting device, 1984–1989 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Drop ceiling support system, 1985–1989 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Lighting Fixtures, 1950–1974 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Louvers, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Twistube, 1982–1987 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Zumbotel, Fixture X, 1993–1997 (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
- Project Files, 1956–1998; Series IV
  This series consists of drawings, sketches, correspondence, and notes documenting Edison Price, Inc. and Nulux, Inc. projects.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by project name.
  - 1 Market Plaza, San Francisco, California, 1992–1994 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 919 Third Avenue, New York, New York, 1990–1991 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Albrecht Kempter Museum, St. Joseph, Missouri, 1992–1993 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Andy Warhol Museum, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1993–1996 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Art Institute of Chicago, Chicago, Illinois, 1986–1987 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Baltimore Museum, Baltimore, Maryland, 1993–1994 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Bank of China, Hong Kong, China, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Battery Park City, New York, New York, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Beierwaltes Residence, Loveland, California, 1994–1995 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, New Haven, Connecticut, 1961–1980 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - BMW Showroom, New York, New York, 1967–1986 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Brandywine River Museum, Chadds Ford, Pennsylvania
    - Project Records, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Drawings, 1983–1984 (Box 43)
  - Bronfman Residence, New York, New York, 1995–1996 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Brunswick Building, Picasso Accent Light, Chicago, Illinois, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Canary Wharf, London, England, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Canary Wharf, Morgan Stanley, London, England, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Chase Manhattan Headquarters, New York, New York, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Cincinnati Art Museum, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1990–1991 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Cisneros Main Library, New York, New York, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Citicorp, New York, New York, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Collins Place, Melbourne, Australia, 1971–1973 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Denver Art Museum, Denver, Colorado, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - First Unitarian Church, Rochester, New York, 1961–1962 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Freer Gallery of Art, Washington, District of Columbia, 1992–1993 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Frost Brothers Department Store, Fort Worth, Texas, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Grand Rapids Museum, Grand Rapids, Michigan, 1992–1993 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Guggenheim Museum, New York, New York, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Guggenheim Museum, Bilbao, Spain, 1995–1996 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Guggenheim Museum, Bilbao, Spain, 1995–1996 (Box 14, Folder 1-3)
  - Haj Terminal, Saudi Arabia, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Philip Hart Building (Hart Senate Office Building), Washington, District of Columbia, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Hartford Fire Insurance Co., Chicago, Illinois, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Hirschhorn Museum, Washington, District of Columbia, 1974, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Hollins College Library, Roanoke, Virginia, 1996–1997 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Holy Angels Church, Chicago, Illinois, 1989–1991 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Huntington Library, San Marino, California, 1993–1994 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - J. Paul Getty Center, Los Angeles, California, 1992–1996 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Marlborough-Gerson Gallery, New York, New York, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Mary Boone Galley, New York, New York, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - McCormick Place, Chicago, Illinois, 1983, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Merrill-Lynch Office, New York, New York, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Metropolitan Museum, New York, New York
    - Aitkin Gallery, 1993–1995 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - European painting retrofit, 1996–1998 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - National Aquarium, Baltimore, Maryland, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - National Airport, Washington, District of Columbia, 1993–1995 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - National Gallery, Washington, District of Columbia, 1985–1994 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Nelson Atkins Museum, Kansas City, Missouri, 1991–1994 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - New York University Village Tower, New York, New York, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Paul, Weiss, Rifkind, Wharton, and Garrison, New York, New York, 1984–1985 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Pequot Museum, Mashantucket, Connecticut, 1996–1997 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Philadelphia Museum of Art, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Ruttenberg Studio, New York, New York, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - San Francisco Library, San Francisco, California, 1992–1994 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - San Francisco Museum of Modern Art, San Francisco, California, 1991–1992 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Seagram and Sons, New York, New York, 1956–1985 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Seagram Building lobby and Four Seasons restaurant, New York, New York, 1957–1959 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Shinji Shumeikai Museum, Kyoto, Japan, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Smithsonian Institution, Washington, District of Columbia, 1992–1997 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Upjohn Company, Kalamazoo, Michigan, 1958–1961 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Western Presbyterian Church, Washington, District of Columbia, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Whitney Museum of Art, New York, New York, 1965–1978 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - World Trade Center, New York, New York, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Fixtures and Products, 1965–1999; Series V
  This series consists of drawings, photometric reports, and product brochures for fixtures designed and manufactured by Edison Price, Inc. and Nulux, Inc.
  This series is arranged by company. Folders within the Edison Price, Inc. grouping are arranged by general documentation and fixtures and products. Folders are arranged alphabetically.
  - Edison Price, Inc.
    - General
      - Catalog numbers, Undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Fixture code and catalog number system studies, 1975, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Installation, 1988, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - New designs, 1989–1990 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Photometric reports, 1972–1987 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Photometric reports, DF4, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Photometric reports, DF5, 1976–1977 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Photometric reports, DF6-7, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Photometric reports, DF8-9, 1976–1977 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Photometric reports, DF10, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Photometric reports, DF11, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Point by point charts, Undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Product and fixture descriptions, 1992-1995, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Product brochures, 1981-1985, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Product brochures, 1988–1990 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Produch shop drawings, Circa 1980s (Box 19, Folder 7-8)
      - Tools, production, 1971–1980 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Fixtures and products
      - Autoceil, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Autotrak, drawings, 1977–1985 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Autotrak 2
        - Drawings, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 3)
        - Design, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 4)
        - Sources and quotes, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Barflux, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - DF-12, drawings, 1977–1979 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Darklite
        - Darklite-Metal Halide, drawings, 1975, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
        - Darklite A, drawings, 1968-1969, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
        - Darklite DTT 9/5, Undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
        - Darklite E, drawings, 1977, undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
        - Darklite MR, Undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
        - Darklite PAR/R, 1981, undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
        - Darklite Q, drawings, Undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
        - Darklite Spredlite PAR 20, Undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
        - Drawings and sketches, miscellaneous, 1970-1996, undated (Box 20, Folder 16)
      - Edison Price, Inc. sketches, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Eminent Technology Tonearm 2 and Talisman Virtuoso B Cartridge
        - Equipment profile, 1991–1999 (Box 20, Folder 17)
        - Equipment profile negatives, 1991–1999 (Box 25, Folder 1)
        - Reviews, 1991–1999 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Erco/Darklite, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 18)
      - Fixture DF12-2, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Johnson Kelly lamp, 1965, 1967, undated (Box 42)
      - Luminaire, Undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Moduceil, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Parhoop 30, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Parhoop 38, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Simplux 10, drawings, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Simplux/Baflux, drawings, 1982–1988 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Spreadlite, striplights, drawings, 1986–1987 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Uminair, 1970–1981 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - Visionair, 1981–1983 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Visionair, New York City, 1986–1987 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - Visionair 240 T8 and S 2/40, 1982–1983 (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - Wall mounted flourescent desk light, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Nulux, Inc.
    - Fixture X, research, 1991–1993 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - H-Lux, M-Lux, Marlux, Slotlux, 1995–1997 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Luxtrak, drawings, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Luxtrak LV, 1995–1996 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Metalumen Track, 1996–1997 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - MicroLux, 1993–1994 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - MR WashLux, 1996–1997 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Names for fixtures and pricing, Undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Nulux fixtures and products drawing set, 1989–1995 (Box 41)
    - Nulux sketches, 1990–1991 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Parlux 36, 38, LV, 1991–1995 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Parlux 38, Small Parlux, 1995–1997 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Parlux 56, drawing, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Parlux fixtures, ink originals, Circa 1990s (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Parlux track fixtures, drawings, Circa 1990s (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Parscoop 38, Undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - S-10-S
      - Office mockup, ceiling layouts, tile information, 1990–1994 (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - Drawings, 1989–1990 (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
      - Drawings, 1989–1993 (Box 39)
      - Studies, 1989, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - ShudderLux, Undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Shutterlux, drawing, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Slot-Lite, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - SlotLux 16, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - SpotLux, Undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - SpredLux, MR-16, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - SpredLux, new, 1993–1994 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - SpredLux/MicroLux E Elevator System, 1991–1995 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - SwidLux, 1996–1997 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - Drawings, 1993, undated (Box 40)
    - TRLux4, Undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Slides, Negatives, and Photographs, 1953–1996; Series VI
  This series contains slides, negatives, and photographs documenting the fixtures, products, and projects completed by Edison Price, Inc. and Nulux, Inc.
  This series is arranged by format type. Folders within the format type groupings are arranged alphabetically.
  - Slides
    - Office, Undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Fixtures and products, Circa 1970s-1980s (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Fixtures and products, drawings, Circa 1980s-1990s (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Edison Price, Inc., Circa 1970s (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Landscape and personal photos, Circa 1980s (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Photometric reports, Circa 1970s (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Projects completed, Circa 1960s (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Projects completed, Circa 1970s (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Projects completed, Circa 1980s (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Projects completed, Circa 1990s (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Glass plate negatives
    - Buildings and city scenes, Circa 1990s (Box 27, Folder 1-4)
    - Areaflector, Circa 1950s (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
    - Baltimore Museum of Art, Baltimore, MD, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 3-7)
    - Barbizon-Plaza Hotel chandelier
      - Chandelier, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Center ball, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 9-10)
      - Over ceiling, elevator, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 11-12)
    - Hotel Roosevelt, New Orleans, Circa 1960s (Box 28, Folder 13-14)
    - Knoll Associates Showroom, Chicago, Illinois
      - Showroom, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 15)
      - Darklite, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 16-17)
    - Parscoop, Undated (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Yale University Art Gallery, New Haven, Connecticut
      - Gallery, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 19-22)
      - Exterior, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Negatives
    - American Institute of Architects Medal, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Edison Price, Circa 1960s-1990s (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Edison Price, Inc.
      - Office, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Employees, Circa 1980s (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Portfolio title pages, Undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - EP Track, Par 38, wall washers, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Fixture DF12-2, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Freight elevator, carrier parts, 1981 May 1 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Helmsley Building, windows, Circa 1980s (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Areaflector, Circa 1950s (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Installation, Undated (Box 29, Folder 11)